Hey
In this video I was going to go through
My 2020
It is because Avanza has a summary of
How my and your stock and fund portfolio on Avanza have gone during 2020.
And you can easily go into it
If you look at the address here
So can you get an overview like the one I will show
How your investment has simply gone!
As a thank you for being so many subscribers here now on the channel so I think I should be a bit nice
Show up exactly how it went for me
To show that I am no lying ugly fish that
Yes
Some other social media have
If you have been involved in following the stock exchange last year then you might have a clue to
The stock exchange got a small breed there in March 2020
when the pandemic arose